John Hernandez

Senior Full Stack Developer

Marian Marian

Innovative, task-driven professional with 10 years of experience in web development across diverse industries. Creative web developer dedicated to developing and optimizing interactive, user-friendly and feature-rich websites.

Certified Technician that operates well in team environments in which technology expertise, extensive analytical skills, and strong problem solving abilities are key to success.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Detail-Oriented
- Complex Problem Solver
- Fast Learner

- · Passion and Honesty
- High Quality

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer, ARC Document Solutions

In this role, I learned the best practices and design patterns and developed app integration with REST/SOAP and other APIs for Social media logins, payment processors and other services.

And I translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements effectively.

I delivered 12 small to medium scale web projects with 3 other developers based on popular libraries like React, Angular and Vue.js.

Senior Full Stack Developer, *WillowTree*

While working with the customers in various projects such as sports betting project, I implemented the use of user feedback in program improvements, resulting 50% boost in customer satisfaction rations. In this company, I designed the architecture of project and and developed a user-friendly websites, including optimized check-out page.

Remote Web Developer, Self Employed

While I have been working as a remote developer, I learned how to work with remote teammates and clients.

In the process, I improved my skills to serve your coding needs and I am ready for your project.

I will produce perfect result for you.

04/2012 - 07/2017 Richmond, VA, **United States**

07/2017 - 11/2021 Charlottesville, VA, **United States**

> 02/2022 Richmond, VA, **United States**

SKILLS

Node.js	• • • •	Express JS	• • • •
React	• • • •	Angular	• • • •
Vue.js	• • • •	Next.js	• • • •
Laravel	• • • •	Django	• • • •
Ruby on Rails	• • • •	Symfony	• • • •
JavaScript	• • • •	TypeScript	• • • •
PHP	• • • •	Python	• • • •
PostgreSQL	• • • •	MySQL	• • • •
MongoDB	• • • •	AWS	• • • •
Agile	• • • •	Docker	• • • •

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, *University of Virginia* Graduated with excellence.

04/2008 - 03/2012

LANGUAGES

English $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$